forward2me.com 2016-05-22

# forward2me - Privacy Policy - UK Mailing Address, Mail Forwarding Service, International Package & Parcel Forwarding

**1 General**

1.1 At forward2me we take your privacy seriously. This Privacy Policy (together with our website [Terms of Use](https://www.forward2me.com/website-terms-of-use "Terms of Use") and [Trading Terms](https://www.forward2me.com/terms-of-trade "Terms of Trade")) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

**2 Information about us**

2.1 This site is operated by forward2me Limited (we, our or us). We are registered in England and Wales under company number 07323718. Our registered office is at York House, Green Lane West, Preston, PR3 1PR. Our VAT number is GB994 6929 42.

**3 Information we may collect from you**

3.1 We may collect and process the following data about you:   
3.1.1 details of transactions you carry out through our website www.forward2me.com (the Site) and of the fulfilment of your orders;  
3.1.2 information that you provide by filling in forms on the Site, including, but not limited to, information provided at the time of requesting or subscribing to any service, or becoming a registered user or if you enter any competition or promotion sponsored by us;  
3.1.3 information from surveys that we use for research purposes, if you choose to respond to them;  
3.1.4 communications you send to us, for example to report a problem with or submit a comment regarding the Site;   
3.1.5 and details of your visits to the Site, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and the resources that you access.

**4 IP addresses and cookies**

4.1 We may collect information about your computer including, where available, your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

4.2 For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. They help us to improve the Site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us to:   
4.2.1 estimate our audience size and usage pattern;  
4.2.2 store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise the Site according to your individual interests;  
4.2.3 speed up your searches;  
4.2.4 and recognise you when you return to the Site.

4.3 You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of the Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you use the Site. The "Help" menu of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. For more information about cookies and how to stop cookies being installed or how to delete existing cookies from your hard drive visit the following website: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

**5 How we process and store your information**

5.1 For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998, the data controller is forward2me Limited.

5.2 The data that we collect from you is processed by staff who work either for us or one of our group companies or for one of our service providers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services.

5.3 All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using secure sockets layer (SSL) technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain features or parts of the Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You must not share the password with anyone.

5.4 When you proceed to the Checkout data relating to your order and your personal details will all pass to our server in an encrypted format. As an additional protection for you, our system is designed so that when using our website you are always safely within secure mode (https).

5.5 All payment transactions will be processed on our behalf by one of our payment providers such as PayPal. This means that your credit/debit card details are provided directly to your choice of payment provider and are never revealed to us. We do not store any of your financial details such as credit card numbers. Our payment providers operate a secure server to process your payment details. The payment provider encrypts your credit/debit card information and authorises payment.

5.6 We recommend that you do not communicate your payment card details to anyone, including us, by email. We cannot be responsible for any losses you may incur in transmitting information to us by internet link or by email. Any such loss shall be entirely your responsibility.

5.7 Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. Remember to close your browser when you have finished your user session. This will help to ensure that others do not access your personal information if you share your computer or use a computer in a public places such as a library or internet café.

5.8 If you have any queries about security, please email us at: [info@forward2me.com](mailto:info@forward2me.com).

**6 Transfers of your Personal Information Overseas**

6.1 In order to fulfil your order, your data may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing and/or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**7 Uses made of your information**

7.1 In order to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and, specifically, to fulfil your orders, we may pass on information held about you to our sub-contractors, including delivery service providers. Depending upon the requirements of your individual order, such third parties may be based and/or operate outside the EEA.

7.2 In addition, we use information held about you in the following ways:   
7.2.1 to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have indicated that you wish to be contacted for such purposes by post, email, SMS, telephone or other means of electronic communication;  
7.2.2 to ensure that content from the Site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;  
7.2.3 to allow you to participate in any interactive features of our services, when you choose to do so;  
7.2.4 and to notify you about changes to our services.

7.3 We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about third party goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these, where you have indicated that you wish to be contacted for such purposes by post, email, SMS, telephone or other means of electronic communication. If you do not want us to use your data for direct marketing purposes, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please check or un-check (as directed) the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data.

**8 Disclosure of your information**

8.1 We may disclose your personal information to any affiliated company within our group.

8.2 We may disclose your personal information to third parties:   
8.2.1 in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;  
8.2.2 if we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our customers will be one of the transferred assets;  
8.2.3 or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our website Terms of Use or Trading Terms or other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, or safety or those of our customers or other third parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**9 Your rights**

9.1 You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking or un-checking (as directed) certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data or by following the [unsubscribe@forward2me.com](mailto:unsubscribe@forward2me.com) on any marketing emails we send you. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at forward2me Limited, York House, Green Lane West, Preston, PR3 1PR or [info@forward2me.com](mailto:info@forward2me.com).

9.2 The Site may, from time to time, contain hyperlinks to and from internet sites operated by other organisations. If you follow a hyperlink to any of these sites, please note that they will have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to such sites.

**10 Access to your information**

10.1 The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with that Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee not exceeding £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**11 How to contact us**

11.1 If you have any questions, comments or requests regarding this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us in any of the following ways:

  *     * by email at [info@forward2me.com](mailto:info@forward2me.com);
    * by telephone on +44 (0) 1995 606060 between the hours of 9:00am and 5:30pm; or
    * by writing to us at forward2me Ltd., York House, Green Lane West, Preston, PR3 1PR.

**12 Updates**

12.1 We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time by changing it on the Site. This privacy policy was last updated on 23rd November 2015.
